Guide to the Joe David Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 2000 Acquisition, 1967-2000; 1; 44.13; (55 boxes)
  - Writing, Editorial, and Project Files
    - Memos, poetry reading schedule, letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, many from CCLM, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
    - CCLM memos and letters (not to Joe David Bellamy), NY State Council on the Arts booklet, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
    - CCLM nomination forms, [circa 1977] (Box 17)
    - Collection of CCLM book fair proposals, addressed to Joe David Bellamy, 1979 July 5 (Box 18)
    - Grants Processing Committee materials, 1979-1980 (Box 18)
    - Ford Foundation report, grant applications, resumes, newspaper clippings, 1977-1978; 2 (Box 18)
    - Blank CCLM stationery, Grants Committee letters, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
    - CCLM letters (most not to Joe David Bellamy), letter notifying Joe David Bellamy of Fels Award, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - CCLM Newsletters, letters and memos re: NEA/CCLM controversy, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Distribution, 1976 (Box 18)
    - CCLM Newsletters, reports, 1970-1978 (Box 18)
    - "Informal copy" of two year report, grant notices, 1974 (Box 18)
    - CCLM catalog of literary magazines, newsletters, letters to Joe David Bellamy (most not CCLM related), 1971-1979 (Box 18)
    - CCLM brochures, newsletters, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Press release, itinerary for Albuquerque conference, 1978 (Box 18)
    - Agenda for Board of Directors meeting, Buffalo, 1976-1977 (Box 18)
    - Agenda for Board of Directors meeting, Austin, 1976 November (Box 18)
    - Agenda for Atlanta regional meeting, 1978 November (Box 18)
    - Agenda for Boston regional meeting, 1979 April (Box 18)
    - Agenda for Iowa City regional meeting, 1980 April (Box 18)
    - Agenda for New Orleans regional meeting, 1980 November (Box 18)
    - Agenda for Los Angeles regional meeting, 1979 November (Box 19)
    - Letters to, from CCLM board, 1980-1990 (Box 19)
    - Letters regarding CCLM advisory board membership, 1980 (Box 19)
    - CCLM catalog of literary magazines, Echoes From a Gold Mountain (Asian- American poetry journal), misc. CCLM letters, 1976-1980 (Box 19)
    - CCLM event notices, misc. literary newsletters, 1978-1980 (Box 19)
    - CCLM memos, letters to Joe David Bellamy, newsletters, 1978-1980 (Box 19)
    - Agenda for Seattle Board of Directors Meeting, 1977 November (Box 19)
    - CCLM Ford Foundation report, letters, newsletter, 1975-80 (Box 19)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, CCLM memos, 1980 (Box 19)
    - CCLM guide to organizing book fairs, letters, 1978 (Box 19)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
    - Bills, receipts, press releases, letters, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
    - CCLM letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1979 (Box 19)
    - CCLM memos regarding grants program, letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Receipts, CCLM letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Fiction International, undated (Box 19)
    - Fiction International letters, 1973-1975 (Box 19)
    - Library Journal reviews, 1972-1974 (Box 19)
    - CCLM grants brochure, receipts, 1972-1978 (Box 19)
    - Fiction International budget plans, mission statement, 1972-1976 (Box 19)
    - Fiction International fincances, etc., 1971-1977 (Box 19)
    - Grants brochure, financial report, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Atlanta minutes, panel for editor fellowship, grant materials, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
    - Receipts, CCLM Newsletter, letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1978-1979 (Box 20)
    - Receipts, grant applications, 1972-1975 (Box 20)
    - CCLM Special Assistance Grants applications, 1976-1979 (Box 20)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, mostly from CCLM, 1979-1980; 2 (Box 20)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, most regarding The Falcon, 1970-1973; 2 (Box 20)
    - Letters to Joes David Bellamy, most regarding The Falcon (continued), 1970-1973; 3 (Box 21)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy and others, typed short stories, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
    - Incomplete copy of The Falcon premier issue, book of typefaces, COSMEP bookstore survey, newspaper clippings, address lists, 1970-1971; 2 (Box 21)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1970 (Box 21)
    - The Falcon accepted material, 1971-1972 (Box 21)
    - The Falcon galley proofs, advertisements, letterhead, 1972 (Box 21)
    - The Falcon cover-letters, flyers, COSMEP newsletters, 1972-1975 (Box 21)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1970-1973; 2 (Box 21)
    - The Falcon Vols. 1-5, 1970-1972; 3 (Box 21)
    - The Falcon Vols. 1-5 (continued), 1970-1972 (Box 22)
    - COSMEP Catalog
    - NEA business letters, program flyers, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - NEA memos, newsletters, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Alabama Statewide Arts Council, NEA memos, news on Frohnmayer's resignation, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Articles on Frohnmayer's resignation, literary newsletters, 1992; 2 (Box 22)
    - Transcript of Frohnmayer testimony, clippings on NEA, public television, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Report on National Literary Prize winners of 1980s, various arts organization flyers, form letters, 1989-1992 (Box 22)
    - NEA memos, newspaper clippings, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Frohnmayer's resignation letter, media reactions, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Newspaper clippings on NEA, 1991; 2 (Box 22)
    - AWP and NEA memos, 1991 (Box 22)
    - NEA application guidelines, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
    - NEA reports on promotion and distribution, UMBA newsletter, 1988-1992 (Box 22)
    - NEA memos, newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box 22)
    - NEA report, guide, 1988-1990 (Box 22)
    - NEA application guidelines, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Arts Manager's Toolbox: Financial Management, 1992 January 14 (Box 22)
    - Marjorie Kinnan Rawlings: A Reader, 1989 (Box 22)
    - NEA Research Center reports, 1991-1992 (Box 22)
    - Various arts program brochures, 1991-1992 (Box 23)
    - Teachers and Writers Collaborative 25th anniversary packet, Bravo arts in education packet, 1992 (Box 23)
    - NEA memos, clippings, unopened PBS letter to Joe David Bellamy, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Zill and Winglee: Who Reads Literature?, NEA and other educational brochures, 1985-1991 (Box 23)
    - NEA Annual Report (2 copies), 1989; 2 (Box 23)
    - Sourcebook of Arts Statistics, 1990 April (Box 23)
    - "Book Affair" newspaper inserts, business letters regarding Fiction International, 1975-1981 (Box 23)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy at Fiction International, 1972-1987; 8 (Box 23)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy at Fiction International (continued), 1972-1987; 6 (Box 24)
    - Moral Fiction: covers, notes, advertisements, 1980, undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - Fiction International: proofs, cover ideas, undated (Box 24)
    - Fiction International: cover drafts, award announcements, 1976-1980 (Box 24)
    - Photocopied articles, letters to and from Joe David Bellamy, Fiction International flyers, 1978-1980, undated (Box 24)
    - Photocopied Fiction International: covers, name and address lists, 1979-1981 (Box 24)
    - Photocopied Moral Fiction covers, ms.: Donald R. Stoddard, Models of Suburbia, 1974-1980 (Box 24)
    - Photocopied illustrations, Hayden English, Media and Communication Catalog, 1979 (Box 24)
    - Fiction International: proofs, various short story ms., 1980, undated (Box 24)
    - Short story and review manuscripts, undated; 6 (Box 24)
    - Short story and review manuscripts (continued), undated; 3 (Box 25)
    - Fiction International: pasted proofs, undated; 4 (Box 25)
    - "Moral Fiction Issue:", proofs, in box, undated (Box 26)
    - Fiction International flyers, clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
    - Fiction International fragments, one letter to Joe David Bellamy, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Fiction International: proofs, ads, 1979-1980 (Box 26)
    - Literary catalogs and newsletters, 1981-1982 (Box 26)
    - Newsletters, clippings, address labels, 1976-1983 (Box 26)
    - Address labels, undated; 14 (Box 26)
    - Letters, award flyers, 1970-1973; 2 (Box 26)
    - Foundations, etc., undated (Box 26)
    - Letters, 1980 (Box 26)
    - Letters from Joe David Bellamy, proofs, 1974-1975; 6 (Box 26)
    - Literary Magazine Review, directory for Publishers' Exposition Display, 1973-1982 (Box 26)
    - Fiction International logo art
    - Press releases, letters of praise, 1973-1979 (Box 27)
    - Press releases, address lists, NEA applications and guidelines, 1976-1983 (Box 27)
    - Letters to Fiction International, 1974-1980 (Box 27)
    - Letters from Catherine Petroski, 1981-1983; 3 (Box 27)
    - John Domini ms. and letters, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
    - Newspaper reviews, proofs, 1979-1981 (Box 27)
    - Fiction International proofs, order forms, story reviews, 1980-1982 (Box 27)
    - Renewals, 1981-1983 (Box 27)
    - Outright Orders, 1980-1983 (Box 27)
    - Regular subscription forms, 1979, undated (Box 27)
    - New subscriptions, 1979-1983 (Box 27)
    - Sample copy, back issue orders, 1980-1982 (Box 27)
    - Claims, 1972-1982 (Box 27)
    - Fiction International publicity, 1972-1979 (Box 27)
    - Sample copy of Indiana Review, ad copies, letters, 1982 (Box 27)
    - Grant material, invoices, clippings, 1972-1982 (Box 27)
    - Fiction International reviews, 1979-1981 (Box 27)
    - Fiction International budget: invoices, charges, etc., 1974-1982 (Box 27)
    - Office procedures, invoice forms, change of address letter, 1984, undated (Box 28)
    - Publicity, copyright forms, 1979-1982 (Box 28)
    - Subscriptions, invoices, 1980-1982 (Box 28)
    - Library invoices, advertisements, 1979-1983 (Box 28)
    - Advertisements, copyright information, 1978-1981 (Box 28)
    - A Directory of American Fiction Writers, 1976 (Box 28)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, scraps, Abstracts of English Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
    - Address labels, short story proofs, undated (Box 28)
    - A Directory of American Poets: printing services flyer, 1973, undated (Box 28)
    - Exile's Return letters and files, Joe David Bellamy's curriculum vitae, 1975-1977 (Box 28)
    - The Magazine Co-Op letters and files, 1975-1977 (Box 28)
    - Fiction International ad rates, listings, 1972-1979 (Box 28)
    - Fiction International advertisements, travel receipts, 1974-1976 (Box 28)
    - Fiction International: proofs, cover ideas, undated (Box 28)
    - Fiction International, miscellaneous, undated (Box 28)
    - Foundations, 1972 October 23 (Box 28)
    - Ronald Sukenick press releases, clips, business letters to Fiction International, 1971-1975 (Box 28)
    - Handwritten draft of Fiction International editorial, undated (Box 28)
    - Short story manuscripts, undated; 2 (Box 28)
    - Fiction International typeset, 1976 July 21 (Box 28)
    - Fiction International proof, undated (Box 29)
    - Fiction International Vol. 1 (2 copies), 1973 Fall (Box 29)
    - Story and interview proofs, 1979 (Box 29)
    - Drawings, cover illustrations, undated
    - Fictional International 12: proofs
    - Fiction International 14: Love Stories, Love Poems (4 copies), 1982; 4 (Box 29)
    - Fictional International 14: cover drawings and proofs
    - Fiction International 13: Satin Palms by Elizabeth Inness-Brown (2 copies), 1981; 2 (Box 29)
    - Fiction International 15, 16, 1984-1986 (Box 29)
    - Letter and photograph of Joyce Renwick, miscellaneous, 1982 August 30, undated (Box 29)
    - Proofs for Fiction International 14, 1982; 3 (Box 29)
    - Short story ms., photographs, undated (Box 29)
    - Contributor notes for Fiction International 14, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Fiction International 14: galley proofs, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Fiction International illustrations, advertisements, annotated pages, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Short story and interview ms., 1980, undated; 2 (Box 30)
    - Poem ms., undated (Box 30)
    - Short story and poem ms., undated (Box 30)
    - Short story and poem proofs, undated (Box 30)
    - Typescript sample sheets
    - Unsorted proofs, covers
    - Notes, advertisements for Fiction International and other literary magazines, book cover slicks, 1981, undated (Box 30)
    - Book cover slicks, literary contest announcements, Fiction International press releases, 1981-1982 (Box 30)
    - Catherine Petroski: Gravity and Other Stories, page proofs, [1981?] (Box 30)
    - John Domini: Bedlam, page proofs, 1981 (Box 30)
    - Elizabeth Inness-Brown: Satin Palms, page proofs, [1981?]; 3 (Box 30)
    - Fiction International: page proofs, 1981; 2 (Box 31)
    - AWP newsletter, Fiction International ms. and proofs, 1981 (Box 31)
    - Fiction International ms., proofs, 1981 (Box 31)
    - Short story ms., 1975-1981, undated; 4 (Box 31)
    - Catherine Petroski short story ms., undated (Box 32)
    - Fiction International: 12 ad proofs, 1981 (Box 32)
    - Photographs, typesets, undated (Box 32)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1972-1983; 9 (Box 32)
    - St. Lawrence Award flyers, 1972 (Box 32)
    - Galley proofs, undated (Box 32)
    - Short story and poetry ms., undated (Box 32)
    - Ms., illustrations, photocopies of articles, letters, 1978, undated (Box 32)
    - Ms., letters, receipts, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Typed manuscripts by Asa Baber, undated (Box 32)
    - Typed manuscripts by Asa Baber (continued), undated; 5 (Box 33)
    - Illustration and ms. proofs
    - Baber, Asa. Tranquility Base, master galleys with cover letter, 1979 May 25 (Box 33)
    - Writers' Conference registrants 1979 (Box 33)
    - WC print shop originals, undated (Box 33)
    - WC correspondence, 1979 (Box 33)
    - WC complete file, brochures (empty folder), undated (Box 33)
    - WC 1980 - Judy (Box 33)
    - Inquiries about 1980 Writers' Conference, 1979-1982, undated (Box 33)
    - 1979 WC ads, publicity, brochures (Box 33)
    - WC 1979 faculty bios, correspondence (Box 33)
    - WC 1979 budget, financial account (Box 33)
    - WC letters to writers, undated (Box 33)
    - St. Lawrence University Writers' Conference, 1974 (Box 33)
    - WC daily schedule, 1978 (Box 33)
    - SLU Writers' Conference, inquiries, 1979 (Box 33)
    - WC fellowships, grants, correspondence, 1979 (Box 33)
    - WC 1979 (Box 33)
    - Cover art, undated (Box 33)
    - Cover art, ms. regarding Fiction International, 1977-1978 (Box 33)
    - Fiction International Vol. 8/9 (4 copies), 1977; 2 (Box 33)
    - Fiction International Vol. 13 (2 copies), 1981 (Box 33)
    - Fiction International Vol. 13 (2 copies) (continued), 1981 (Box 34)
    - Strathmore paint sample collection, undated (Box 34)
    - Asa Baber: Tranquility Base and Other Stories (Fiction International 10/11) (5 copies), 1979; 3 (Box 34)
    - John Domini: Bedlam (2 copies]), 1981 (Box 34)
    - Elizabeth Inness-Brown: Satin Palms (2 copies), 1981 (Box 34)
    - Catherine Petroski: Gravity (3 copies), 1981 (Box 34)
    - Fiction International 12 (Moral Fiction) (4 copies), 1980; 3 (Box 34)
    - Fiction International 12 (Moral Fiction) (4 copies) (continued), 1980 (Box 35)
    - Typescripts, page proofs, undated; 5 (Box 35)
    - Fiction International 2/3 (2 copies), 1974 (Box 35)
    - Addressed index cards; Weyerhauser color sample, undated (Box 36)
    - Annotated poetry galleys, undated (Box 36)
    - Writer's Forum brochure, "Poets on Videotape", 1975 (Box 36)
    - Niagara Magazine, with letter to Joe David Bellamy enclosed, 1978 November 25 (Box 36)
    - The Falcon, vols. 2/3, 4-8, 11, 12, 1971-1976; 8 (Box 36)
    - Unmuzzled Ox, vol. 3, no. 2, 1975 (Box 36)
    - New Collage (vol. 1, no. 3), with letter to Joe David Bellamy enclosed, 1971 (Box 36)
    - Skywriting (no. 3), with letter to Fiction International enclosed, 1973 September (Box 36)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy at Fiction International, 1972-1987; 7 (Box 36)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy at Fiction International (continued), 1972-1987; 2 (Box 37)
    - Fiction International envelopes, subscription forms, book review typescript, undated (Box 37)
    - The Best American Short Stories 1975, book cover slick (Box 37)
    - Fiction International, 1975 (Box 37)
    - Reviews, [1976] (Box 37)
    - Book and magazine proofs, [circa 1970] (Box 37)
    - Short story typescript, Fiction International 6/7 cover slick, advertisement rates sheet, 1975 (Box 37)
    - Cancelled Fiction International checks, letters to Joe David Bellamy, contributor list, 1975-1980 (Box 37)
    - Short story and article typescripts, undated (Box 37)
    - Fiction International 4/5 cover slicks, proofs, typescripts (2 boxes), 1975; 6 (Box 37)
    - Abstracts of English Studies, 1976 March (Box 37)
    - Fiction International 4/5 (2 copies), 1975; 2 (Box 38)
    - Fiction International 6/7 (4 copies), 1976; 2 (Box 38)
    - Interviews for American Poetry Observed (photocopies and typescripts), undated; 2 (Box 38)
    - Letters to Joe David Begllamy, literary flyers, newsletters, 1974-1978 (Box 38)
    - Interviews, undated (Box 38)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38)
    - Diane Wakoski interview, copy of Iowa Daily Planet, 1977, undated (Box 38)
    - American Poetry Review, interviews, 1977, undated (Box 38)
    - Photocopies of interviews, undated (Box 38)
    - Letters to/from Joe David Bellamy, 1972-1982 (Box 38)
    - Typescript from James Tate, interview, 1978 October 30 (Box 38)
    - Photocopies of interviews, notes on interviews in other magazines, letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1982, undated (Box 38)
    - Writing magazine, interview typescripts, 1979-1981 (Box 38)
    - Interviews, typescripts and photocopies, 1973-1982; 4 (Box 38)
    - Interviews, typescripts and photocopies (continued), 1973-1982; 2 (Box 39)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1977-1980 (Box 39)
    - Interviews, 1976-1980; 2 (Box 39)
    - Index cards, listing bibliographical information on articles and interviews, undated (Box 39)
    - Letters to Joe David Bellamy, evaluations from Joe David Bellamy, literary newspapers and event pamphlets, 1980-1998 (Box 40)
    - Literary magazines, event flyers, newsletters, 1963-1990; 3 (Box 40)
    - Fiction International press releases, newspaper clippings, book cover slicks, letters to Joe David Bellamy, 1973-1983 (Box 40)
    - Bennington writing workshops: story manuscripts, applications, program information, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Antioch writers' workshop: faculty lists, flyers, applications, 1992-1993; 2 (Box 40)
    - Epic Used Book Shop (Yellow Springs, OH) Stationery, Antioch Record, 1964 November 13 (Box 40)
    - Poetry Pilot (8 copies), 1990 September (Box 40)
    - Saturday Review, New York Arts Journal, The Creative Urge, 1970-1978 (Box 40)
    - Fiction International 12 (Moral Fiction) brochures, order forms, 1980 (Box 40)
    - Coda (4 copies), AWP Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 41)
    - Ohioana Quarterly, 1990 Fall (Box 41)
    - The Ohio Review, 1980 (Box 41)
    - Parnassus Poetry in Review, 1979 Spring (Box 41)
    - Empty envelope with Erica Jong return address, undated (Box 41)
    - Proofs for short stories, no author listed, 1979 July 11 (Box 41)
    - Saturday Review, New York Times Book Review, Harpers, 1975-1978; 2 (Box 41)
    - New York Times Book Review (4 issues, 7 duplicates)
    - Tom Wolfe letters, articles, reviews, 1972-1990; 4 (Box 41)
    - Joe David Bellamy Letters
      - Alberts, Laurie, 1981-1999 (Box 41)
      - Anderson, Bobbie, 1980-1981 (Box 41)
      - Baber, Asa, 1970-1980 (Box 41)
      - Banks, Russell, 1976-1991 (Box 41)
      - Barber, Phyllis, 1982 (Box 41)
      - Barthelme, Rick, 1979-1988 (Box 41)
      - Beattie, Ann, 1977-1983 (Box 41)
      - Benedikt, Michael, 1974-1985 (Box 41)
      - Blaise, Clark, 1975-1977 (Box 41)
      - Barnett, Andrea, 1999 November 25 (Box 41)
      - Bourjaily, Vance, 1970-1978 (Box 41)
      - Boyle, Denis, 1973 January 6 (Box 41)
      - Boyle, Tom, 1979-1991 (Box 41)
      - Carruth, Hayden, 1989 March 6 (Box 41)
      - Cherry, Kelly, 1984-1999 (Box 41)
      - Cox, Betsy, 1981-1984 (Box 41)
      - Dodd, Susan, 1981 (Box 41)
      - Doland, Jerry, 1972 July 27 (Box 41)
      - Fulton, Len, 1989 May 15 (Box 41)
      - Godwin, Gail, 1975-1977 (Box 41)
      - Hall, Donald, 1991 (Box 41)
      - Hawkes, John, 1976 June 14 (Box 41)
      - Henderson, Bill, 1987-1998 (Box 41)
      - Humphries, Jo, 1992 August 28 (Box 41)
      - Inness-Brown, Elizabeth, 1981-2000 (Box 41)
      - Irving, John, 1992 August 28 (Box 41)
      - Jerome, Judson, 1989 May 2 (Box 41)
      - Klinkowitz, Jerry, 1973-1981 (Box 41)
      - Laughlin, James, 1980 (Box 41)
      - List, Gordon, 1978-1989 (Box 41)
      - Macaulie, Robie, 1975-1977 (Box 41)
      - McMurtry, Kenneth, 1982 April-August (Box 41)
      - Moore, Lorrie, 1981-1999 (Box 41)
      - Morris, Wright, undated (Box 42)
      - Murray, G.E., 1980-1988 (Box 42)
      - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1971-1989 (Box 42)
      - Ochester, Ed, 1992 September 7 (Box 42)
      - Phillips, Jayne Anne, 1978-1979 (Box 42)
      - Plumley, Stanley, 1992 (Box 42)
      - Poverman, Buzz, 1977 March 22 (Box 42)
      - Price, Reynolds, 1967-1993 (Box 42)
      - Randolph, Leonard, 1976 November 24 (Box 42)
      - Reed, Ishmael, 1977-1980 (Box 42)
      - See, Carolyn, 1996 January 1 (Box 42)
      - Simmons, Charles, 1979 July 4 (Box 42)
      - Siyaki(?), Carol, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
      - Sontag, Susan, 1972-1973 (Box 42)
      - Sukenick, Ron, 1970 August 21 (Box 42)
      - Tate, James, 1976-1978 (Box 42)
      - Thompson, Jean, 1979 February 6 (Box 42)
      - Villanueva, Alma, 1982-1991 (Box 42)
      - Williams, Miller, 1970-1992 (Box 42)
      - Wilson, Rob, 1972-1992 (Box 42)
      - Brown, Beth, 1981 (Box 42)
      - Casey, Pam, 1982 (Box 42)
      - Glassman, Steve, 1981 (Box 42)
      - Kenary, Jim, 1982 (Box 42)
      - Langlois, Ron, 1981 (Box 42)
      - Lium, Marie, 1981 (Box 42)
      - Parnum-Brown, Roger, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
      - Petrucci, Marvyn, 1981-1983 (Box 42)
      - Pope, Susan, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
      - Taylor, Steve, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
      - Tudish, Kevin, 1981-83 (Box 42)
      - Wells, Valerie, 1982 (Box 42)
      - Yup, Paula, 1981 (Box 42)
    - Goddard College writing program material, 1981-1983; 4 (Box 42)
    - New York Times Book Review with review of Wolfe's Purple Decades
    - Norwich University / Vermont College, correspondence and notes, 1981-1982; 2 (Box 42)
    - Text proposals, 1970-1976 (Box 42)
    - Freshman English proposals, undated (Box 42)
    - Text ideas, contacts, royalty arrangements, 1972-1978 (Box 42)
    - Apocalypse, contents, undated (Box 42)
    - University of Arkansas Press brochure, correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 42)
    - Holt author's guide, 1968 (Box 42)
    - Joe David Bellamy correspondence with Holt Rinehart Winston, authors' guides, other writers' comments on Joe David Bellamy's work, 1970-1993 (Box 42)
    - Joe David Bellamy correspondence with Lippencott, 1970-1973 (Box 43)
    - Joe David Bellamy interview with Robert Boles, non-Bellamy ms., undated (Box 43)
    - Apocalypse: original drafts, undated (Box 43)
    - Apocalypse: reviews, undated (Box 43)
    - Publisher correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 43)
    - Publicity materials, 1970-1976 (Box 43)
    - Brief handwritten biographies, undated (Box 43)
    - Cover art for Atomic Love, undated (Box 43)
    - Handwritten preface, other notes for Apocalypse, undated (Box 43)
    - Typescript preface to Apocalypse, non-Bellamy articles, undated (Box 43)
    - Apocalypse preface and tables of contents, undated (Box 43)
    - Apocalypse tables of contents, typescripts and photocopies of Joe David Bellamy's and others' work, undated (Box 43)
    - Galley proofs for Apocalypse, stamped "uncorrected proofs" and marked "my copy", undated (Box 43)
    - Proofs and typescripts for Atomic Love and other works, 1992 December 1; 3 (Box 43)
    - Cover proofs for New Writers of the 80s
    - Letters regarding publishing rights, 1970-1981; 3 (Box 44)
    - Poetry copyright assignments, title page proofs for Olympic Gold Medalist